

Personal

Name

Priyadarshini Rajmohan

Address

D-F2, Sudarshan Urban Ville, Thanthai Periyar St, Cholavaram Nagar, Nagalkeni, Chrompet 600044 Chennai

Phone number 9524277129

Email

priyasathyasai@gmail.com

Interests

Painting

Cooking

Playing Badminton

Priyadarshini Rajmohan

Passionate person with skills in IT. Worked in web based application projects and provided technical support to end-users, leveraging broad based expertise to handle problem identification. Experienced in JAVA and SQL and in front end technologies like Angular, HTML5, CSS, bootstrap. Looking forward to work with leading software companies to give my complete contribution with my experience for active participation and to lead the team, meeting the target on time and achieving success for walk of my life and for the company.

Work experience

Senior System Engineer

Jul 2020 - Present

Infosys, Chennai

- Worked effectively to deliver Software programs of the functionalities/requirements as expected on time with code quality.
- Always challenge current situation and provide ideas to improve workflow and maintain code structure and guidelines.
- Performing impact analysis and completing the sprint tasks on time with quality
- Collaborating with team for better delivery of programs.
- Performing proper unit testing and integration testing using Karma.
- Analyzing the error trends aimed at reducing down time.
- Resolving technical issues.
- Worked on screen conversions and new screens in Ford Recall Management as Java and Angular Developer

System Engineer

Jul 2018 - Jul 2020

Infosys, Chennai

- Deliver software programs on time.
- Performing impact analysis and completing the sprint tasks on time with quality
- Collaborating with team for better delivery of programs.
- Always challenge situations and provide ideas to improve workflow and maintain code structure and guidelines.
- Performing proper unit testing and integration testing using Karma.
- Analyzing the error trends aimed at reducing down time.
- Performed automation process to reduce work time and to process data more effectively.
- Monitoring, recoding and responding to request for support.
- Worked on screen conversion and new screens in Toyota Financial service and Ford for single global system as Java and Angular Developer

System Engineer Trainee

Jan 2018 - May 2018

Infosys, Mysore

- Trained in JAVA ,Angular and bootstrap.
- Developed Blog search engine for sports category with quick response.
- Performing Analysis and completing the project on time with quality.

Education and Qualifications

B.E (Computer Science and Engineering)

Jun 2014 - Apr 2018

Kongu Engineering College, Perundurai

Graduated with 92% CGPA with First class designation

Strength and Weakness

Strength: Dedicated, Creative, Focused

Weakness: Adamant, Too Detail Oriented, Too Punctual

Skills

Programming skills	
Team lead	
Problem Solving	
Analytical Ability	
Perseverance	
Collaboration	
Critical Thinking	

Technical Expertise

Web Technologies: Angular 8,9 ,HTML5,Bootstrap,CSS3

Technologies: JAVA/J2EE,Spring,RDBMS

Testing Tool: Karma **Version Control**:Git

Achievements

Awarded for being flexible and dedicated resource. For gaining the customer confidence in short span of time and also for coming up with automation idea and developed the tool to automate the reports which saves monthly 12 hours of manual effort.

Certifications

Infosys Internal Course

- Infosys Certified Angular Professional
- Infosys Global Agile Developer Certification

Courses	
Go Java Full Stack with Spring Boot and Angular Udemy	Apr 2021 - Apr 2021
Client Orientation Infosys Internal Course	Jun 2020 - Jun 2020
Problem solving for success Infosys Internal Course	Jun 2020 - Jun 2020
Developing presentation layer and web services of Enterprise application using spring Infosys Internal Course	Jun 2020 - Jun 2020
CSS3 Infosys Internal Course	May 2020 - May 2020
HTML5 Infosys Internal Course	Nov 2019 - Nov 2019
Getting started with Angular	Nov 2019 - Nov 2019